oh no don't say good day to you this day
of your time how are you all alright
alright we have entitled this
transmission interdimensional portals
and where to find them now this
transmission will be a little bit all
over the map specifically the one in
your hands we will be dealing with a few
energy portals not all of them we will
start with some and over time we will
introduce more and more and more of them
in future transmissions but for now if
you will regard the maps you have been
given we can begin
hello Bashar I may you good day so I
asked questions about belief systems I
suppose yes so I have a fear and this
fear I'm not afraid of what happens
after I die yes I'm afraid of how I will
die well how do you imagine that you
will die that seems so fearful I don't
know I I don't know how I'm gonna die so
it it scares me the idea of safety maybe
pain or so you are saying that you
simply prefer not to experience pain is
that what you're saying yeah that you
would like to die simply and easily yeah
all right well then go ahead and do that
okay what is it that you believe will
determine that transition yeah and I
think that's maybe it is that I perhaps
I think that it's set up for me like
it's something that is inevitable and
when that it happens I so you understand
that you set it up yes yeah yeah so do
you believe that you chose a
particularly nasty way to die well I see
yeah I don't think anyone comes in
saying I want to die like this
oh but sometimes they do because it
depends on what purpose that serves now
yes it's true for the most part people
may forget that they have a choice and
have made a choice and so they may just
simply let it run its course and
experience the idea of pain but since
you're asking the question that
obviously means you have some conscious
recognition that it's possible to change
that yes or you wouldn't be asking the
question you wouldn't even consider the
possibility that you might be able to
consider something different
so the fact that you can ask the
question is usually an indication that
you can choose right now a way that
would work better for you yes yeah so
how would you like to transition in your
sleep or floating in a pool
I just peaceful just like yeah well then
again there is nothing preventing that
if you believe that it doesn't really
serve you if there's no lesson to be
learned that you can't learn in life by
experiencing the idea of a painful
transition then there's no need to
experience it that way yes and remember
in that sense death is really just like
waking up from a dream because physical
reality is a dream you do understand
that you're in spirit right now yes none
of you leave spirit that's your natural
state you are just dreaming that you've
left
that's what physical reality is a
portion of your greater being in
non-physical reality is pretending that
it's no longer in the spirit realm but
you are
right now the greater portion of you and
this portion that is seemingly the whole
of your identity as a physical being to
the version of you that is in spirit
right now is just about the same as the
size of your fingernail
that's your physical being to the spirit
that you are do you understand so just
like you wake up in the morning from a
dream yes is that painful no well then
same idea you're just gonna wake up and
go oh that seemed so real
but now I know that was just a dream and
this is who I actually am yes yeah does
that sound more preferable yeah all
right
then it can be that way for you unless
of course you choose to be a masochist
yeah I'd prefer and feel like you need
to punish yourself for something at the
end of your life is that something you
believe you need no all right then there
is no need to experience that yes
yeah can be over in a blink in fact if
you really are actually at any point in
your life done all you have to do is lie
down and close your eyes and say I'm
ready to go and then count to 10 if you
can open your eyes at the end you're not
done because it can be that easy if you
actually are done you can just say I'm
done
lie down close your eyes and go yes yeah
is this helping
yeah it's helping no all right you feel
a little bit more relaxed about your
death
[Laughter]
a little bit if you want we will be
happy to show up at the moment of your
death with pitchforks you could show up
but maybe no pitchforks just you know a
friendly hello but we would only do that
to make you laugh and that way you get
to die laughing
[Applause]
[Music]